(Sheldon:)Consequently,
if Amy and I choose
(Sheldon:)to bring new life
into this world,
(Sheldon:)it will be accomplished
clinically,
(Sheldon:)with fertility experts in a lab
with petri dishes.
(Sheldon:)Which reminds me--
(Sheldon:)you have broad hips
and a certain corn-fed vigor.
(Sheldon:)Is your womb available
for rental?
(Leonard:)Still digging the Shamy?
(Penny:)Look, Sheldon,
(Penny:)before you race off to
the fertility clinic,
(Penny:)you might want
to think about--
(Penny:)uh, gee, I don't know--
(Penny:)maybe actually spending
some time with her.
(Sheldon:)You mean dating?
Yeah.
(Sheldon:)I can't date Amy.
Why not?
(Sheldon:)She's not my girlfriend.
(Penny:)Okay, look, don't think of it
as dating a girlfriend.
(Penny:)Think of it as, uh...
(Penny:)getting to know
the future mother of your child.
(Raj:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)I hadn't considered that.
(Sheldon:)I suppose she will have
to have access to our progeny.
(Sheldon:)And you don't think
I can achieve
(Sheldon:)the required intimacy
via text messaging?
(Penny:)Probably not.
(Sheldon:)Huh.
(Sheldon:)It would appear as if